{
    "subject": "resource/Duchy_of_Brunswick",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/German_gold_mark",
    "human_readable": "The currency of the Duchy of Brunswick is German gold mark.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9426043033599854,
            "question": "What were the factors that led to the adoption of the German gold mark as the currency of the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9032115340232849,
            "question": "What was the currency of the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8737037777900696,
            "question": "When did the Duchy of Brunswick use the German gold mark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8709097504615784,
            "question": "What type of mark was used as currency in the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8614562749862671,
            "question": "What other currencies were used in Europe during the time period when the Duchy of Brunswick utilized the German gold mark?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8328173756599426,
            "question": "Are there any records or artifacts that mention the German gold mark in the context of the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8024415373802185,
            "question": "What historical significance does the German gold mark hold for the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7729987502098083,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of transactions or economic activities that involved the German gold mark in the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7435692548751831,
            "question": "Was German gold mark used in other regions besides the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.697655200958252,
            "question": "How did the use of the German gold mark impact trade within the Duchy of Brunswick?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of the Duchy of Brunswick is German gold mark.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8921_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was German gold mark used in other regions besides the Duchy of Brunswick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8921_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide examples of transactions or economic activities that involved the German gold mark in the Duchy of Brunswick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8921_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical significance does the German gold mark hold for the Duchy of Brunswick?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8921_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8921_64.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information about the Duchy of Brunswick using the German gold mark as its currency. Instead, they mention that the Duchy of Brunswick used thalers and pfennigs, among other currencies or coin types. Therefore, the statement is incorrect based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "The currency of the Duchy of Brunswick during the time period specified (1771-1815, 1813-1815) was not German gold mark but Thaler. The change to German gold mark occurred after 1814 and not during the lifespan of Duke Frederick William mentioned in the context information.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text states the currency of the Duchy of Brunswick was the Thaler from 1499-1814.  It also mentions German gold marks in other contexts, but not as the specific currency of the Duchy of Brunswick.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context provides information about the Duchy of Brunswick using thalers as currency (1794 KM-398 Graded vf details By NGC references), and mentions 1 Pfennig being a value within the Thaler currency (1/288 of a Thaler). There is no mention or evidence supporting that the German gold mark was used during this time period.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}